#### **Admission Counselor**

# **MAULI GOR**

## **Objective**

Working as an admission counselor from 3 year, understand the front person, convincing into the objective given by an organization is the thing, am performing always at my best. Leading the team, with polymath to SOP's of company.

## **Experience**

Nov 2022 - Current

#### Admission Counselor Praajasv foundation

Follow-up for new enrollments, answering phone calls to parents, sales information from sales companies, resolving questions for new and existing graduates, reviewing admission rules, planning parent meetings, reviewing and announcing results Improvements, etc. Students need a change of branch and lead to the monitor of the transportation center.

July 2021 - Oct 2022

## Admission Counselor iNurture Education Solutions Private Limited

Tracking of new admissions, active phone calls to student parents, information sales company sales, clearing doubts of new and existing alumni, reviewing admissions rules, scheduling meeting with parents, review results and presentation of results improved, more students need branch transfers, leads to monitoring transport center.

December 2018 - March 2021

#### **Admission Counselor** Aakash Institute

Getting the leads of new admission, active call to the student's parents, summarizing the data into the salesforce, clearing the doubts of new and existing students studying and coming, process the admission protocol of new students, arranging the periodic meeting with parents, reviewing the results and analytical presentation of results improved, many students need the branch transfer, leads to have look on the logistics facility

May 2018 - July 2018

#### **Receptionist** *Tirupati Forms Limited*

Complain handling on toll free number, arranging the meetings, handling the calls for inquiry, understanding to customers on price terms when they get quote on new enquiry from us, Sending the complaints to the respective department, Handling the attendances of an employees

#### **Education**

April -2018

# BBA Marketing

Gujarat University

April -2015

**HSC** 

GHSE Board

April 2013

SSC

**GSE Board** 

## Skills

- Data analysis
- Project
- managementSales forecast
- $_{\square} \ \ \text{achievement}$
- □ Problem solving
- $_{\Pi}$  Polymath
- Calm and convincing Can
- lead the team Summarizing the past events for future forecast

#### **Interests**

Love to listen the music, to play the cards, like to have street foods, and most one is dancing, giving the tuitions who wants to learn the dance during their various programs.

#### **Contact**

Borisana Road, At Kalol Ta- Kalol, Dist-Gandhinagar Gujarat – 382721 +91-9033621224 +91-8866491262 mauligor2311@gmail.com